Guide to the American Dance Festival Photographic Materials Collection, circa 1930-2008
American Dance Festival Archives
- Duke University, 1978-2008
  - Other Events, Dance Town Hall, 1979, (35 mm color negatives) (Box 37)
  - Other Events, Doris Duke Award Luncheon, 1998, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Other Events, Emerging Generations Program, 1981, (8 x 10 b&w negatives) (Box 37)
  - Other Events, Made in France Program, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negatives) (Box 37)
  - Other Events, Modern Dance Caucus, 1985, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Other Events, undated, 1997, (8 x 10 b&w negatives) (Box 37)
  - Other Events, Vanity Fair magazine shoot, 1984, (prints) (Box OS2)
  - Parties, 1994 (2 folders), (prints) (Box 24)
  - Parties, 1995, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Parties, 1996, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Parties, 1996, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Parties, 1998, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Parties, 1999, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Parties, 2000, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Parties, 2006, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Parties, circa 1980, (35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Parties, circa 1992, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Parties, Cloud Gate Reception, 2002, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Posters and Reproductions, undated, (35 mm slides) (Box 37)
  - Project Dance, 2000, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Publications, Aesthetic and Cultural Significance of Modern Dance, illustrations Philippine Dancers, circa 1984, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Scholarship Presentation, 1982, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Scripps/ADF Award, 1981-1982, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Scripps/ADF Award, 1981-2001, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Scripps/ADF Award, 1982, 1989, 2000, (prints) (Box OS2)
  - Scripps/ADF Award, 1982-1984 (Hanya Holm, Paul Taylor, Merce Cunningham), (4 x 5 b&w negatives, 35 mm contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Scripps/ADF Award, 1983-1986, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Scripps/ADF Award, 1987-1989, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Scripps/ADF Award, 1989 (Doris Humphrey, Charles Weidman, Jose Limon), (35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Scripps/ADF Award, 1993, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Scripps/ADF Award, 1993, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Scripps/ADF Award, 1993-1994, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Scripps/ADF Award, 1993-1994 (Talley Beatty, Trisha Brown), (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Scripps/ADF Award, 1995-1996 (Helen Tamiris and Pearl Primus, Meredith Monk), (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Scripps/ADF Award, 1996-1999, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Scripps/ADF Award, 1997 (Anna Halprin), (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Scripps/ADF Award, 1998-1999 (Pina Bausch, Nicholas Brothers), (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets, 35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Scripps/ADF Award, 2000-2001 (Shen Wei, Pilobolus), (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Season Dedication, 1996, (prints) (Box OS2)
  - Season Dedication, 1996, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Season Dedication, 1998-1999, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets, 35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Season Dedication, 1998-2000, 2002, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Season Dedication, 2000-2001, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Showings and Rehearsals, undated, (35 mm slides) (Box 37)
  - Special Events, Distinguished Teacher Award (Daniel Nagrin), 1992, (4 x 5 b&w negatives, 8 x 10 b&w negatives) (Box 37)
  - Stepping into History Workshop for Professionals, 1993-1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Student and Teacher, Artist and Audience: 65 Years of the ADF, 1998, (35 mm color negatives) (Box 37)
  - Student Auditions, 1978, 1994, Registrations, 1978, 1995, (35 mm slides) (Box 37)
  - Student Outdoor Concert, 1979, (35 mm slides) (Box 37)
  - Students, 1978-1980, (35 mm slides) (Box 37)
  - Students, 1979-1989, (35 mm b&w contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Students, 1980-1981, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Students, 1985, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Students, 1988-1989, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Students, 1994, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Students, 1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Students, 1995-1996, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Students, 1997, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Students, 1997-1998, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Students, 2002, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Students, Asian Cultural Council, 1997-1998, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Students, Asian Cultural Council, 1999-2000, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Students, Four Week School, 1993, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Students, Four Week School, 1993-1994, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Students, Four Week School, 1996, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Students, Four Week School, 1997-1998, (35 mm slides, 35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets, 2 1/4 b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Students, Four Week School, 1997-1999, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Students, Four Week School, 1999-2001, (35 mm color negatives and contact sheets, 2 1/4 color negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Students, Four Week School, 2001-2002, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Students, International, 1993-1994, (35 mm b&w negatives and contact sheets) (Box 37)
  - Students, undated, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Students, undated, (8 x 10 b&w negatives) (Box 37)
  - Therapy, 1979, (35 mm slides) (Box 38)
  - Unidentified, Performances, undated (2 folders), (4 x 5 b&w negatives, 8 x 10 b&w negatives, 35 mm slides) (Box 38)
  - Unidentified, Students, undated, (35 mm slides) (Box 38)
  - Unidentified, undated, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Unidentified, undated (4 folders), (4 x 5 b&w negatives, 8 x 10 b&w negatives, 35 mm b&w negatives, 35 mm b&w contact sheets, 35 mm slides) (Box 38)
  - Workshops, 1979, (35 mm slides) (Box 38)
  - Workshops, 1996, (35 mm b&w negatives) (Box 38)
  - Workshops, 1996-1998, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Young Choreographers and Composers in Residence Program (YCCP), 1983, (prints) (Box 24)
  - Young Choreographers and Composers in Residence Program (YCCP), 1989, (8 x 10 b&w negative) (Box 38)
- Unidentified, Undated
  The Unidentified series contains images that have yet to be identified or dated, primarily 8 x 10 black and white prints.
  - Unidentified, Undated (3 folders), (prints) (Box 38)